样本
随机样本
分子结构
gt
GPT3.5
GPT4
GPT3.5ICL
GPT4ICL
galactica
LLaMo
ours
CC=Cc1ccc2oc(-c3ccc(Oc4cc(-c5oc6ccc(C=CC)cc6c5C)ccc4O)cc3)c(C)c2c1
The molecule is a natural product found in Piper
aequale with data available.
The molecule is a complex polyol structure featuring multiple sugar units, specifically a branched
polysaccharide with numerous hydroxyl (-OH) groups and acetylated amine functionalities.
The molecule is a complex organic compound featuring
multiple aromatic rings and ether linkages.
The molecule is a complex polysaccharide with multiple sugar units and acetylated amino groups, likely derived from a natural source with
potential biological activity.
The molecule is a complex polysaccharide with multiple acetylated amino sugar units, commonly
found in natural sources such as bacterial or plant polysaccharides, with data available.
The molecule is a natural product found in Piper
aequale with data available.
The molecule is a natural product found in
Krameria erecta with data available.
The molecule is a
natural product
found in Piper
aequale with data
available.
CCCCCCCCC=CCCCCCCCCC(=O)O
The molecule is the (Z)-stereoisomer of 10-
nonadecenoic acid.
The molecule is a complex polyol with multiple hydroxyl (–OH) groups, featuring a long carbon chain
with several double bonds and branching.
The molecule is a long-chain fatty acid known as oleic acid.
The molecule is a complex polysaccharide derivative with multiple hydroxyl groups and a sulfate group, likely derived from a natural source
with potential biological activity.
The molecule is a natural product found in marine organisms, particularly in soft corals, with data
available.
The molecule is a natural product found in the fungus
Aspergillus niger with data available.
The molecule is a natural product found in
Monascus purpureus with data available.
The molecule is
the stereoisomer
10-nonadecenoic
acid, a long-chain
fatty acid.
COC1C(COC2CC(O)C(N)CO2)OC(n2c3ccccc3c3c4c(c5c6ccccc6[nH]c5c32)C(=O)N(C)C4=O)C(O)C1O
The molecule is a natural product found in
Actinomadura melliaura with data available.
The molecule is a complex polycyclic compound featuring multiple sugar-like structures and ester
functionalities.
The molecule is a complex organic compound featuring a
polycyclic structure with multiple functional groups.
The molecule is a complex natural product with multiple sugar and aromatic moieties, likely derived from a plant source, exhibiting potential
biological activity.
The molecule is a complex lipid with multiple ester and ether linkages, likely derived from natural
sources such as plants or marine organisms, with data available.
The molecule is a natural product found in the fungus
Aspergillus fumigatus with data available.
The molecule is a natural product found in
Actinomadura melliaura with data available.
The molecule is a
natural product
found in
Actinomadura
melliaura with
data available.
CCCC=CC=CC1Cc2cc(O)cc(O)c2C(=O)O1
The molecule is a natural product found in
Aspergillus with data available.
The molecule is a complex carbohydrate derivative featuring multiple sugar units and functional
groups, including acetyl and amine functionalities.
The molecule is a naturally occurring organic compound known
as alpha-tocopherol, which is a form of vitamin E.
The molecule is a complex polysaccharide derivative with multiple hydroxyl and acetyl groups, indicating potential biological activity and
structural significance in various natural products.
The molecule is a complex carbohydrate derivative, likely a glycosylated compound, with data
available.
The molecule is a natural product found in the fungus
Aspergillus niger with data available.
The molecule is a natural product found in
Aspergillus with data available.
The molecule is a
natural product
found in
Aspergillus with
data available.
CC(C)c1cc2c(c(O)c1O)C13CCCC(C)(C)C1C(O)C2OC3O
The molecule is a natural product found in Salvia
aspera with data available.
The molecule is a complex polyphenolic compound featuring multiple aromatic rings, methoxy and
hydroxyl functional groups, and several sugar moieties.
The molecule is a complex organic compound featuring a
polycyclic structure with multiple hydroxyl groups.
The molecule is a complex natural product with multiple functional groups, including methoxy, hydroxyl, and carbonyl groups, suggesting
potential bioactivity. It may be derived from a plant source, indicating its possible role in traditional medicine or as a phytochemical.
The molecule is a natural product with data available.
The molecule is a natural product found in the leaves
of the plant.
The molecule is a natural product found in
Lepecanthus vestitus with data available.
The molecule is a
natural product
found in Salvia
aspera with data
available.
大原子数分子
分子结构
gt
GPT3.5
GPT4
GPT3.5ICL
GPT4ICL
galactica
LLaMo
ours
CC(=O)NC1C(OC2C(O)C(CO)OC(OC3C(CO)OC(OC4C(O)C(CO)OC(OC5C(CO)OC(OC6C(O)C(CO)OC(OC7C(CO)OC(OC8C(O)C(CO)OC(OC9C(CO)OC(OCC%10OC(O)C(NC(C)=O)C(OC%11OC(CO)C(O)C(O)C%11O)C%10O)C(NC(C)=O)C9O)C8O)C(NC(C)=O)C7O)C6O)C(NC(C)=O)C5O)C4O)C(NC(C)=O)C3O)C2O)OC(CO)C(OC2OC(CO)C(O)C(O)C2O)C1O
The molecule is a natural product
found in Dracaena draco with
data available.
The molecule is a complex polysaccharide derivative
featuring multiple sugar units interconnected by glycosidic
bonds, with several hydroxyl (-OH) groups and acetylamine
functionalities.
The molecule is a complex glycopeptide structure
composed of multiple sugar units linked together,
forming a branched polysaccharide chain.
The molecule is a natural product
found in Ozoroa insignis with data
available.
The molecule is a natural product
found in Dracaena draco with
data available.
The molecule is a natural product found
in the leaves of the plant, Crocus
sativus with data available.
The molecule is a natural product
found in Aspergillus flavus with data
available.
The molecule is a natural product
found in Dracaena draco with
data available.
C=CCCC=CC=CC=CCCC=CC(O)C(O)C1OC(C(O)C(O)C(=C)CCC(O)C2CC(O)C(O)C(C(O)C(O)C=C(C)CCC(O)CC(O)C(O)C(C)C(O)C(O)CC=CCC(O)C=CCCCCCOS(=O)(=O)O)O2)CC(O)C1O
The molecule is a natural product
found in Amphidinium with data
available.
The molecule is a complex polyol with multiple hydroxyl (-
OH) groups and a long carbon chain featuring several
double bonds.
The molecule is a complex polyhydroxylated
macrolide with multiple conjugated double bonds
and a sulfonate ester group.
The molecule is a natural product
found in Aconitum hemsleyanum
with data available.
The molecule is a natural product
found in Amphidinium with data
available.
The molecule is a natural product found
in Piper aequale with data available.
The molecule is a natural product
found in Aglaia lawii with data
available.
The molecule is a natural product
found in Amphidinium with data
available.
CCCCCCCCCC(=O)OC1C(OC2C(C)OC3OC4C(OC(CCCCC)CCCCCCCCCC(=O)OC2C3O)OC(C)C(O)C4O)OC(C)C(OC2OC(C)C(OC(=O)C(C)CC)C(O)C2OC(=O)C=Cc2ccccc2)C1OC1OC(C)C(O)C(O)C1O
The molecule is a natural product
found in Ipomoea pes-caprae
with data available.
The molecule is a complex polycyclic compound featuring
multiple sugar-like structures and ester linkages.
The molecule is a complex carbohydrate derivative,
specifically a highly substituted oligosaccharide
ester.
The molecule is a colorless,
flammable liquid.
The molecule is a natural product
found in Ipomoea pes-caprae
with data available.
The molecule is a natural product found
in Piper aequale with data available.
Molecule SMILES.
The molecule is a 3-hydroxy-4-
hydroxymethylpyridine.
The molecule is a natural product
found in Ipomoea pes-caprae
with data available.
CC(=O)NC1C(OC2C(O)C(CO)OC(OCC3OC(O)C(NC(C)=O)C(OC4OC(CO)C(O)C(OC5OC(CO)C(OC6OC(CO)C(O)C(O)C6O)C(OC6OC(C)C(O)C(O)C6O)C5NC(C)=O)C4O)C3O)C2O)OC(CO)C(OC2OC(CO)C(O)C(O)C2O)C1O
The molecule is an amino sugar.
The molecule is a complex carbohydrate derivative
featuring multiple sugar units and functional groups,
including acetyl and amine groups.
The molecule is a complex glycosylated
compound, specifically a glycopeptide, consisting
of multiple sugar units linked to an acetylated
amine group.
The molecule is a natural product
found in Citrus medica and Citrus
hassaku with data available.
The molecule is an amino sugar.
The molecule is a natural product found
in the leaves of the plant, Cinnamomum
camphora with data available.
The molecule is an amino sugar.
The molecule is an amino sugar.
COc1cc(C=CC(=O)OC2C(OC3C(Oc4cc5c(OC6OC(CO)C(O)C(O)C6O)cc(O)cc5[o+]c4-c4ccc(O)c(O)c4)OC(COC(=O)C=Cc4ccc(O)cc4)C(O)C3O)OC(CO)C(O)C2O)cc(OC)c1O
The molecule is a natural product
found in Microcystis aeruginosa
with data available.
The molecule is a complex polyphenolic compound
featuring multiple aromatic rings and sugar moieties.
The molecule is a complex polyphenolic
compound, specifically a glycosylated flavonoid
derivative.
The molecule is a natural product
found in Streptomyces with data
available.
The molecule is a natural product
found in Microcystis aeruginosa
with data available.
The molecule is a natural product found
in the fungus Aspergillus fumigatus with
data available.
The molecule is a natural product
found in Arundina graminifolia with
data available.
The molecule is a natural product
found in Microcystis aeruginosa
with data available.
样本
1

